puremobile.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy - USA - Pure Mobile

  * Our Commitment to Your privacy
  * The information we collect
  * Why we collect it
  * Personal information use and disclosure
  * Our use of cookies
  * Transmitting material to us
  * Our eMails to you
  * Consent
  * Updates to this policy

Last updated: April 6, 2012. 

Thank you for choosing Pure Mobile - www.puremobile.com - hereinafter called the Site. We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. This Privacy Policy also explains the steps we have taken to secure your personal information. Finally, this Privacy Policy explains your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. By visiting the Site directly or through another site, you accept the practices described in this Policy.

## Our commitment to your privacy

At Pure Mobile, we acknowledge that online business brings new opportunities and new responsibilities. We embrace the opportunity to provide personalized eCommerce services for unlocked cell phone, wireless devices and their related accessories to you in a highly secure environment. Despite, our infrastructure being among the most technically advanced and secure networks, we share with you the responsibility of controlling the exchange, storage, and use of selected personal information.

Confidentiality is a priority for us and we take all the necessary measures to safeguard the strict privacy of the personal information contained in your file, whether you purchase your unlocked cell phone, wireless devices and related accessories from us or not.

## The information we collect

Pure Mobile collects information you agree to provide us with when registering to purchase unlocked cell phones, tablets, notebooks and related accessories. Information—such as your name, civic and email address, telephone number—is collected and retained. We may also use this information to keep you informed of upcoming promotions or new products that may be of interest to you. Anonymous information is collected mostly through standard analysis of our web-server and analytic log files. We may use this data to monitor which areas of the site are used most and to determine which areas we need to focus on improving. This data is used exclusively by Pure Mobile so that we may continue to improve the value of the services and information on the website.

Entering personal data on Pure Mobile is not only easy but also safe. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) protocol, which is among the best Internet security software in the world along with GeoTrust for securing the exchange of confidential data. This security technology encrypts the personal information that you send us (including things like names, addresses, emails, telephone numbers and credit card numbers), so it cannot be read by anyone as it travels over the Internet. Moreover, for added security we scramble your credit numbers in the event that our data base is compromised by external forces. We will evaluate and adopt new security technology as it becomes available.

## Personal information use and disclosure

**Internal Use**

We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve the Sites’ content and layout, to improve outreach and for our own marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to the Site.

**Communications with you**

We will use your personal information to communicate with you about the Site and your orders and deliveries. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register with us. We may send you a service-related announcement on the rare occasions when it is necessary (for example, if we must temporarily suspend our service for maintenance.) Also, you may submit your email address for reasons such as to register for a contest or sweepstakes; to request us to notify you of new brands, new product styles or promotions; to sign up for email newsletters and special offers; or to sign up for the our email Alert service. If you submit your email address, we use it to deliver the information to you. We always permit you to unsubscribe or opt out of future emails (see the opt out section, below, for more details). Because we have to communicate with you about orders that you choose to place, you cannot opt out of receiving emails related to your orders.

**External Use**

We want to provide you with excellent service and to offer you a great selection. We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone other than to affiliates under Pure mobile’s control, except that:

As do most catalogue and Internet retailers, we sometimes use others to perform specific functions on our behalf. When we disclose information to these service providers, we disclose information to help them to perform their service. For example, in order to deliver products to you, we must share some information. We partner with third parties (such as the U.S. Postal Service, United Parcel Service, and Federal Express) to ship products, to ensure delivery, and so that we can obtain feedback, improve the quality of our service, and measure and improve the quality of the service of the third party. In the example of shippers, we provide them some personally identifiable information such as your name, shipping address, email, and phone number.

## Why we collect it

You can choose to visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. If you do provide specific consent to obtain information, it is always to gather only the information needed to serve you better, and provide you with the right unlocked cell phones, tablets, notebooks and related accessories at the right time and at the right price.

## Our use of cookies

Pure Mobile's eCommerce engine uses cookies to allow and facilitate your user session with us. During the quotation process, cookies store session information to ensure that the data is passed on in proper sequence from step to step. The cookie itself is stored on your own PC and does not contain any personal information. Pure Mobile also uses third party Analytics Code to help us better evaluate the effectiveness of our advertising and to determine the behaviour of visitors on our website in an effort to provide you with the most ongoing enhanced customer experience.

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of the Site. We have to use cookies to enable you to select products, place them in an online shopping cart, and to purchase those products. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase. THE SITE’S COOKIES DO NOT AND CANNOT INFILTRATE A USER’S HARD DRIVE TO GATHER A USER’S CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION. Our cookies are not “spyware.”

## Transmitting material to us

Pure Mobile is not responsible for any damages resulting from the interception, loss of, or modification of any e-mail you have sent.

We would like to remind you that information sent by e-mail is not secure. We recommend that you take care to not include confidential information, such as your policy number, personal information, etc., when sending e-mail..

## Our E-Mails to you

We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of your e-mail address and not using it inappropriately. E-mail addresses collected are not be shared, sold or disclosed to any organizations that are not authorized members of Pure Mobile and will only be used for the purpose of e-mailing you information about our products and services or to communicate with you information about any unlocked cell phone, tablet, notebook and related accessories offers likely to interest you. In addition, e-mails that we send do not contain personal or confidential information. You have the right to be removed from our mailing list at any time by selecting the 'Unsubscribe' link at the bottom of every email.

## Consent

Your consent is required for the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information by us. When you voluntarily provide certain Personal Information to us, You are also giving your implied consent (if express verbal or written consent has not otherwise been requested) for us to collect, use and disclose that personal information to fulfill the identified purposes. The applications, forms and documents We use include points pertinent to your authorization, which allows us to collect, use or disclose personal information concerning You. It is important to read all such points carefully.

We may disclose such information in response to requests from law enforcement agencies conducting investigations; subpoenas; a court order; or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud or if someone uses or attempts to use the Site for illegal reasons or to commit fraud.

## Updates to this policy

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on the Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us at sales@puremobile.com

Effective April 6, 2012
